Free U.s. Shipping On Orders Over $89 (Excludes items with truck symbol, AK & HI)

Search  

    ### teaching

    [
    
    ### Focus Helpers
    
    Help struggling students focus and learn with these helpful products.
    
    shop now](https://nationalautismresources.com/focus-helpers/)

    ### Toys & Gifts

    [
    
    #### Need Help Finding
    
    Perfect Gift Ideas?
    -------------------
    
    ### Holiday Gift Guide
    
    Shop top toys & gifts for developmental skills.
    
    SHOP GIFT GUIDE](https://nationalautismresources.com/autism-toys/)

    ### Calming

    [
    
    ### Calming Favorites
    
    Browse some of our favorite, most popular calming products
    
    SHOP NOW](https://nationalautismresources.com/calming-products/calming-favorites/)

    ### Sensory & OT

    [
    
    ### Sensory Room Furniture
    
    Create a multi-sensory area with these interactive & calming products
    
    SHOP NOW](https://nationalautismresources.com/sensory-ot/sensory-room-furniture/)

    ### Resources

    [
    
    ### 2024 Catalog
    
    See what's new for 2024! Browse our digital version of our catalog.
    
    Download .pdf](https://nationalautismresources.com/content/2023NARCatalog.pdf)

Search  

* [](javascript:void(0);)
    
    #### Individual Account
    
    I am **shopping as an individual** and not ordering with a school or organization and may purchase with my personal credit card.

    #### Educator Account
    
    I am **shopping as a member of a school, business or organization** and may purchase with a PO or credit card.

Free U.S. Shipping On Orders $59+. (Excludes items with truck symbol, AK & HI)

Search  

* [Teaching](javascript:void(0);)
    
    ### Teaching
    
    Go Back

* [Toys & Gifts](javascript:void(0);)
    
    ### Toys & Gifts
    
    Go Back

* [Calming](javascript:void(0);)
    
    ### Calming
    
    Go Back

* [Sensory & OT](javascript:void(0);)
    
    ### Sensory & OT
    
    Go Back

* [Resources](javascript:void(0);)
    
    ### Resources
    
    Go Back

We’re Here to Help!

[877-249-2393](tel:8772492393) 9am-4pm CST

1. [Home](https://nationalautismresources.com/)
2. [Privacy Policy](https://nationalautismresources.com/privacy-policy/)

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which National Autism Resources collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the nationalautismresources.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by National Autism Resources.

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the siteplace an orderfill out a formrespond to a surveysubscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information,

Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

 **Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

 **How we use collected information**

National Autism Resources collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

* To improve customer service
* Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
* To personalize user experience
* We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
* To improve our Site
* We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
* To process transactions
* We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
* To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
* To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
* To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

**Third party websites**  
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\\'s own terms and policies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
National Autism Resources has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

National Autism Resources

nationalautismresources.com

PO Box 1419, Forsyth MO 65653

877-249-2393

contactus@nationalautismresources.com

Policy Updated at 1:07 PM PST 9/6/18

Close

!

OK Cancel

Footer Start
------------

### Sign up for our Email Specials

Join our eNewsletter for updates, tips, and news!

Email Address

### Account

### Support

### Purchase Orders

* Quote Request

### Contact Us

P.O. Box 1419  
Forsyth, MO 65653

Phone: [877-249-2393](tel:8772492393) Hours: 9am-4pm CT Fax: [877-259-9419](tel:8772599419)

### Follow Us

©2024 National Autism Resources.

All Rights Reserved.

Site Design by [EYStudios](https://eystudios.com/).

Are You an Educator?  
GET SPECIAL PRICING!

If you work at a school, sign up for an [Educator Account](https://nationalautismresources.com/b2b-log-in/) to access **educator discounts on all orders.**
